import { Question } from "../components/MovieQuiz";

export const pnrData: Question[] = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the town where 'Parks and Recreation' is set?",
    options: ["Pawnee", "Scranton", "Eagleton", "Dunder Mifflin"],
    answer: "Pawnee",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the director of the Parks and Recreation Department at the start of the series?",
    options: ["Ron Swanson", "Leslie Knope", "Chris Traeger", "Ben Wyatt"],
    answer: "Ron Swanson",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Leslie Knope's favorite food?",
    options: ["Waffles", "Pancakes", "Burgers", "Pizza"],
    answer: "Waffles",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Tom Haverford's business venture?",
    options: [
      "Rent-A-Swag",
      "Entertainment 720",
      "Snakehole Lounge",
      "Tom's Bistro",
    ],
    answer: "Rent-A-Swag",
  },
  {
    question: "Who does Leslie Knope marry?",
    options: ["Ben Wyatt", "Ron Swanson", "Tom Haverford", "Andy Dwyer"],
    answer: "Ben Wyatt",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which character is known for their love of breakfast food and disdain for government?",
    options: ["Ron Swanson", "April Ludgate", "Andy Dwyer", "Tom Haverford"],
    answer: "Ron Swanson",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Andy Dwyerâ€™s band?",
    options: ["Mouse Rat", "Rat Mouse", "Scarecrow Boat", "Demon Llama"],
    answer: "Mouse Rat",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What holiday do Leslie and Ben invent to celebrate their friends?",
    options: [
      "Galentine's Day",
      "Treat Yo' Self Day",
      "Pawnee Appreciation Day",
      "Harvest Festival",
    ],
    answer: "Galentine's Day",
  },
  {
    question: "Which character is famous for the catchphrase 'Treat Yo' Self'?",
    options: [
      "Tom Haverford and Donna Meagle",
      "Leslie Knope and Ann Perkins",
      "Ron Swanson and April Ludgate",
      "Ben Wyatt and Chris Traeger",
    ],
    answer: "Tom Haverford and Donna Meagle",
  },
  {
    question: "Who becomes the mayor of Pawnee at the end of the series?",
    options: ["Garry Gergich", "Leslie Knope", "Ben Wyatt", "Tom Haverford"],
    answer: "Garry Gergich",
  },
  {
    question: "What was Ben Wyatt's nickname when he was a teen mayor?",
    options: ["Ice Town", "Little Mayor", "Ice King", "Mayor Benji"],
    answer: "Ice Town",
  },
];
